if you're anything like me well then you
also
hate hopping out of bed in the morning
and your legs basically giving out on
you from a hardcore leg day the day
before now thankfully massages are
pretty easy to get nowadays especially
in the form of a massage gun but since
there's so many for you to choose from i
figured i'd go ahead and compare two of
my favorites on the market the theragun
prime and the hyper ice hypervolt ii
what is up everybody it's jake back in
the barbing garage gym with another
comparison review for you all today this
time i've got the theragun prime in the
hyper ice hypervolt 2. in this review
i'm going to compare both of these
massage guns and help you decide which
one needs to be in your hands alright so
before i get started today i have to let
you know we've reviewed a lot of massage
guns on barbin.com and if you want to
browse our best list just go ahead and
search barbin best massage guns you can
find out for yourself which ones that we
like the best
[Music]
okay so let's kick this off with the
similarities between these two massage
guns first and foremost they both offer
powerful percussive massages if you
don't know what a percussive massage is
it's essentially rapid and repetitive
pressure that's applied by the massage
heads mixed in with vibrational therapy
from the motors and the massage guns
both of these massage guns have powerful
percussive speeds for you to use to work
out any soreness that you may be
experiencing from you know a hardcore
training session or even just life in
general you know we all tend to get
pretty stiff sometimes so this is a
really good way to work out that
soreness that you may be experiencing
both of these massage guns come with
multiple attachments for you to use this
is going to be great it's going to add
some variety to your massages that way
you can focus on specific parts of your
body and really get back to feeling like
your normal self there's a companion app
provided by both of these companies
which is super super helpful in my
opinion because they're full of guided
routines that show you how to properly
use the massage gun i'ma dig into all
that in just a minute but it's really
cool because all the routines are gonna
be based off of the activities that you
participate in so it's really gonna be
based around use specifically now both
of these massage guns also have
bluetooth capabilities that can be
paired up with that companion app that
way you can control the speed setting
directly through your phone which is
also really cool and lastly both of
these massager guns are actually
available for the exact same price
okay so let's talk about those
differences between these two massage
guns there's actually a lot more
differences than there are similarities
so let's talk about the actual design
first and foremost i think it's pretty
clear you can see that they're pretty
different right so with the theragun
prime you have an ergonomic handle right
here which is technically three
different handles built in one with this
triangle design and with the hypervolt 2
i mean you only have one handle right
here so it's obviously pretty different
the attachments are also different as
well so with the theragun prime these
are a little bit more forgiving in my
opinion than with the hypervolt 2
because they're softer right so with the
hypervolt 2 the majority of these are
made from a hard plastic so that's
obviously going to hurt if you
accidentally hit a bone which i
definitely wouldn't recommend you do
that now with the theragun prime
attachments don't get me wrong like i
know i said they're more forgiving
they're a little bit softer made from
like a foam type material but they still
pack a punch don't get it twisted
whatsoever so you can definitely work
out those deep knot issues in your deep
tissue that you might have the theragun
prime actually has more speed settings
than the hypervolt ii so it's five to
three so you technically do have a
little bit more versatility with your
speed settings but the hypervolt 2 has a
longer battery life so hypervolt 2 is
going to last you around three hours
while the theragun prime is designed to
last you about two hours now that
battery life for both of them is going
to change depending on what speed
setting you have it on as well as how
much pressure you're applying to your
body so keep that in mind now both of
these massage are going to show you how
much battery life is left but they do it
in different ways so with the theragun
prime you have three different led
lights above the speed changer while
with the hypervolt 2 you have an led
light at the base of the handle it's
going to change colors as it starts to
die on you so when it's green it's fully
charged it's going to cycle to yellow
then orange and red as it dies now
the charging is going to be different as
well so with the hypervolt 2 it's going
to take you about three hours for it to
fully charge all the theragun prime it's
about an hour and a half or so now i
know i mentioned both of these massage
guns do come with a companion app super
helpful yeah they're pretty similar in
the way they function but they're also
pretty different so with the theragun
prime you actually have a little bit
more options for you to choose from and
the way everything is done with the
guided routines is pretty different as
well so the hypervolt 2 is going to have
guided videos of somebody actually using
the massage gun and you're supposed to
follow along during that time with the
theragun prime you're going to have
diagrams on where you need to position
the massage gun as well as which
direction for it to go in now i don't
think one's better than the other but
it's a little bit different so it's
definitely something worth mentioning
and lastly as you can tell you know
hypervolt 2 is just bigger overall so it
may be a little bit more difficult if
you want to take it on the road
[Music]
all right so let's talk about the money
now as i mentioned earlier both of these
massage guns are available for the same
price which is right around
hundred dollars now you can purchase
both of these from the thera body
website or the hyper ice website
there are some other options out there
for you as well you can head over to
various websites and they actually do
carry these massage guns and those are
going to vary in terms of financing you
can definitely finance these purchases
it's going to split up into either you
know four interest-free payments or
monthly payments for you know up to two
years for some of those options so just
check it out and just kind of see you
know how you're feeling and what works
best for you specifically now comparing
these to the rest of the market i'm not
gonna lie they're pretty expensive right
300 for a massage gun
that's not cheap so
definitely more designed for somebody's
gonna use it you know on a daily basis
for the most part but
because of the multiple attachments
because of how effective they are
i personally think both of these are
worth that price tag
okay so let's talk about the build now
and some of the features that you'll
find with the theragun prime let's talk
about the build first and foremost made
from a hard plastic it feels really
sturdy in my hands doesn't feel too
creaky i guess you could say like some
plastic you know what i'm talking about
you know how that feels now feels like
you can handle some bumps and bruises if
you were to drop it
be careful still because it is plastic
but i think it's gonna be okay
on the off chance it does fall out of
your hands i really like this ergonomic
handle right here three different
handles basically in one this front grip
is about six inches in diameter while
the back one and the bottom one about
four and a half inches in diameter so a
little bit of variety right there it's
about eight inches tall and with an
attachment it's about eight inches from
front to back now you have a little bit
of
rubber feeling right here on your
handles to give you a little bit of a
good grip while you're using it which is
really nice now you'll have five
different led lights pop up right here
when you turn it on it's gonna signal
what speed setting you're on and right
above this arrow right here you're gonna
have three led lights it's gonna signal
how much battery life is left so if this
does die on you remember it's designed
to last right around two hours you can
expect it to charge take about an hour
and a half for it to fully charge and
get that full battery life again it
weighs about 2.2 pounds it's pretty
lightweight i mean most massaging guns
are pretty lightweight but yeah it's
about 2.2 pounds you're not gonna get
too fatigued while you're using it which
is really nice now the attachments some
of my favorites that i've used in my
past
they're pretty forgiving you know
they're a little bit foamy but they're
still firm especially you know this cone
attachment and the thumb attachment
right there you're still gonna be able
to work out those knots that you have
and
but if you do you know on the off chance
you hit a bone they're not really gonna
hurt which is really nice plus you get
this little travel bag right here which
i really like you can fit everything in
here toss it in your bag you can hit the
road with no issues whatsoever
[Applause]
[Music]
okay so it's transitioned to the
hypervolt 2 now this is also made from
really sturdy plastic in my opinion
feels really solid i don't feel like
it's going to break if it falls out of
my hands now the handle diameter is also
right around six inches it's an oval
shape with a rubber grip on here i
really like that it's gonna give you you
know a solid grip while you're using it
it's about nine and a half inches tall
and with an attachment it's a shade
under eight inches from front to back
now these attachments but for the most
part they're all made from a hard
plastic except for this ball attachment
and this cushion attachment which this
one is probably my favorite out there
it's gonna be great for the sensitive
areas such as your neck and around your
hands and your wrists this is the one to
go to right here now
instead of having a bag for you to toss
your massage gun and all your
attachments in you only have a bag for
the actual attachments but you know it's
still pretty nice keep everything in one
specific spot now
despite it being you know larger
than the theragan prime it's actually a
little bit lighter so the hypervolt 2
weighs 1.8 pounds it might not make that
much of a difference but it is in fact
lighter now if this does in fact die on
you it's going to take you around three
hours or so for it to fully charge
remember it has a three hour battery
life which is also like the therigon
prime is going to change depending on
what speed setting you have it on and
how much pressure you're applying
against your body now
i really like how you have a pressure
sensor right here so these three lights
once it's on that third light that's
showing you like that's for basically
max pressure you might need to dial it
back a little bit now you have three led
lights right here on the side it's going
to show you what speed setting you're on
and to change the speed actually the
power button so you're going to tap that
power button it's going to cycle through
the available speeds that you have and
instead of having led lights appear to
signal how much battery life is left
it's actually down here at the base of
the handle and as i mentioned you know
it's going to cycle from green to yellow
to orange to red
as it starts to die on on top of all
that you also have a set of
international outlet attachments for you
to use so that way if you travel
overseas you can still charge this thing
in another country which is really cool
now the battery life here is supposed to
last around three hours and if it dies i
would expect it to take around three
hours as well for it to fully charge
all right so let's go ahead and do a
walk around with both of these massage
guns i'm going to start with the
hypervolt 2. let's talk about the
attachments first as i mentioned you
know most of these are made from a hard
plastic minus this ball attachment and
the cushion i really like how you have
some added versatility with your
massages you know each individual
attachment is meant for a specific
region of your body so that's really
nice now in terms of changing the
attachment it's really easy as you may
assume just simply pull out
it's going to pop out for you you can
pop a new one in
just push it in tight you'll know when
you can't just you know yank it out
without actually trying that it's nice
and secured so turn it on simply press
and hold on this power button for a
couple of seconds
you'll see this light come on down here
now i've been using mine so it's not
fully charged right now so it's yellow
means i do need to charge it here soon
or else this is gonna turn to orange and
then red die on me so
that's your bluetooth light right here
that blinking blue light means you know
it's not paired up but it will
those are your pressure sensor led
lights right there and then right here
on the side that's your speed setting so
to change the speed just simply press
the button you'll see that light up it's
going to kick in on you
and cycle through
it's pretty loud
and then you just press and hold again
to turn it off now if this does die on
you
simply plug it in down here at the base
of the handle for a handful of hours you
know about three hours or so and it's
going to be good to go for you now if we
transition over to the theragun prime
let's talk about the attachments again
first you know as i mentioned these are
a little bit more forgiving in my
opinion but
they still pack a punch right especially
this cone attachment and the thumb
attachment they're gonna really target
those deep tissue areas and really work
out those knots that you may have now
when you go to turn the theragun prime
on it's going to kick in right away so
we're going to press and hold this power
button right here in between these two
speed changer buttons
and it cuts right on now press up on
this up arrow right here
it's also pretty loud it might be a
little bit quieter though than the
hypervolt 2. maybe something to think
about so if you're watching netflix you
know you're watching whatever i'm going
to turn the volume up a little bit i'm
going to turn this down now
and this is actually is fully charged at
the moment and we have all three led
lights lit up right here it's going to
cycle all the way down to one until it
dies on turn it off okay so in terms of
changing your attachments it's pretty
much the exact same thing as the
hypervolt ii simply pull out
you do want to make sure that these
beads right here on either side line up
with the inside of your new attachment
that you're going with that way
nice and secure it's not gonna fall out
on you
if this massage gun dies on you remember
battery life's right around two hours
simply plug it in the front right here
to take about an hour and a half for it
to fully charge
[Music]
okay so which massage gun should you buy
well honestly y'all you cannot go wrong
with either one of these massage guns
they both offer powerful percussive
massages to work out any soreness you
may be experiencing and in my opinion
they're also a great way to warm up
before you exercise because they're
going to increase the blood flow in
whatever region you're using them on
at the end of the day though you just
really need to consider you know the
features and what's going to be make or
break for you so the hypervolt 2 comes
with an extra attachment and a longer
battery life but in my opinion the
therigon prime has more forgiving
attachments
two extra speed settings and the
companion app is a little bit more
detailed but once again you know since
they are the exact same price you can't
really go wrong with either one of these
well y'all that's all i have for today's
comparison on the theragun prime and the
hypervolt 2. both of these massage guns
are a great way to recover from any
soreness you may be experiencing as well
as warming up before you exercise
you know they're essentially the same
product both companies just went about
it in a different way thanks for
watching y'all i hope this video was
really helpful and i was able to show
you exactly what to expect with both of
these massage guns as well as maybe help
you make that decision on which one to
go with as always stay tuned for my next
video but for now head over to
barbin.com you can read more about this
comparison right here just type in
barbind theragun prime versus hypervolt
2 review and you can read all the
details that i discussed here today i'll
see y'all next time
[Music]
you